Guide to the Yale School of Drama Photographs and Posters
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Yale School of Drama posters, 1998-2003; Accession 2009-A-092
  - The Imaginary Invalid, 1999 (Box 1)
  - Tree, 2000 (Box 1)
  - Rice Boy, 2000 (Box 1)
  - The Caucasian Chalk Circle, 2000 (Box 1)
  - Heaven, 2000 (Box 1)
  - The Way of the World, 2001 (Box 1)
  - The Black Monk, 2003 (Box 1)
  - The Black Dahlia, 2003 (Box 1)